so this bull run I'll probably be one of
the only people in the world who makes
over $100 million in meme coins so to
back that up I'll just show you a couple
of my public wallets that you all know
about over $11 million in this wallet
with Brett over a million between these
Wallets on Bobo over a million or what
was just a million dollars and
resistance dog before the pullback on
this wallet and I just got a new
computer and my other one shut off and
it literally won't turn back on so I
still need to import some of my C
phrases but if you watched my other
videos youve seen some of my tweets you
guys all know my public wallet address
on ton blockchain is 1999. ton someone
who has over a million dollars on Pony
which I haven't imported my Phantom
wallet but like I said if you believe me
cool if you don't I don't care uh anyone
who's been following me for the last few
years you all know these positions and a
lot of these wallets and I know a ton of
you guys track these wallets already so
as someone who literally just on public
wallets has around 13 to 15 million
right now I think I am probably one of
the best people in the world who can
make a video about how to actually
become a millionaire meme coins not
someone who's made like 10,000 one time
got lucky on a little trade and just a
singular trade right and now was making
videos about how to do it no I've done
it on many trades many times executed
and time stamped on this channel for
example you guys have watched and uh you
know been along the ride on a lot of
these and so yeah I here's the thing the
bull market is not going to last forever
uh you can see this bull market over
here lasted uh 8004 days this one 1,66
days and the current one we're in has
been going on for about 738 days so if
you go based off the previous bull runs
you know you're looking at another 100
to 300 days for altcoins cuz actually
that's what we're looking at right now
is a chart of all altcoins outside of
the top 10 coins by market cap so once
the bull Market's over and the market
goes into a downtrend since most of you
guys don't know how to short the market
uh you know you end up just losing money
and coins are not going to be able to
run as far you're not going to be able
to do as many x's and the golden
opportunity and window of time to make
money will be over so with the time that
we have left in the bull run which looks
to be like another 100 to 300 days what
would I do to maximize my chances of
success if I was someone who had less
than
$100,000 what would I do to make sure
that I get into the millions and so you
know you probably heard it them say it
before like if you strip a billionaire
of his businesses you start him at zero
and he has to start over again he'll get
back into the millions faster with ease
right cuz he already has the knowledge
and experience to do it again whereas
you take someone who maybe even has a
head start right so say you reset me to
$0 but you have
$200,000 there's a very good chance I
beat you to a million before you do with
$200,000 to my $ Z that's because I know
a lot of things see a lot of patterns
and just have some you know Insight that
you probably don't I'm going to run you
through a couple examples of some of my
mistakes that you can learn from so you
don't have to repeat them and then I'm
going to go over some of the wins and
some of the thought process that led me
to literally just showing you right
there about 13 million on public wallets
just on this computer right now remember
I'm on a new computer man I don't even
have all my wallets in this one right
now but let's get into it so about a
year and a half ago I think it was we
can go back and see the exact date
there's this meme coin called Bitcoin
and this was one of my biggest misses
ever and this was a coin that I liked a
lot when it came out I thought it was
really funny and I thought it was very
unique and there wasn't a lot of
competition at the time there wasn't
that many meme coins or at least good
ones and so we go back to this is May of
2023 so about a year and a half ago so
it launched and then it died down and
then it did this little double bottom
which once again remember it's around 7
8 million market cap here dies down and
I remember dude it was night time it was
like 3:00 a.m. uh for me and this was at
700k market cap I was so tired I was
probably working all day and so I said
okay when I wake up I'm going to buy
this because I have a feeling that it's
not actually dead and and it's going to
you know revive from here so 700k I wake
up bro the next day this thing is at 34
million market cap so it's already up 4
to 5x from when I went to sleep and said
I was going to buy when I wake up so I'm
pissed I'm like well there goes my entry
it's gone I'm not going to buy the [__]
5x higher than where I was just about to
buy it at the absolute bottom so time
goes by I never bought it remember when
I woke up dude it was around here uh
around 3 to four million Market cup I
could have easily got in there 4 to 5x
higher but that ended up being one of my
biggest misses um where today I'd
probably be one of the top 30 top 25
biggest whales in Harry Potter had I
bought that day whenever I went to sleep
instead at like 3:00 4:00 a.m. so
anyways that was a mistake but here's
the beauty in that this mistake ended up
leading me to one of my biggest wins and
meme coins which I still hold to this
day Bobo right I have over a million
dollars in Bobo so notice this pattern
and just remember this okay let's Zoom
back in CU you probably didn't pay
attention enough or remember basically
it launched and then it Fizzles out and
does this double bottom before it
revives okay so let's go and find a
chart of Bobo now and you're going to
notice Bobo did the exact same thing and
so when this meme coin presented me the
same opportunity that I messed up over
there on Harry Potter Obama Sonic 10 euu
okay you're going to notice this Bobo
did the exact same thing so it launched
just like Harry Potter and guess what
bam Fizzles out double bottom right one
two and so when I saw this again man I
was like oh man I [__] this up on
Harry Potter I am not messing this up
again and I was just buying Bobo all
down here because I noticed it I knew
this was a strong meme I knew that it
had a great narrative right this is the
bearish character you have this at one
million you have Pepe at 1 billion so to
me it was just very clear that the
counterpart character right the bearish
character would have value in relation
to the bullish character now I get it
bullish character you would think has
more value bullish character is the
character that a lot of people more
people know about Pepe than Bobo but
nonetheless you can still make a very
strong case that okay Bobo the bearish
character is also going to have a strong
value then if the bullish character has
a lot of value and I was right about
that so it went from being what looked
like dead to many people where they
don't want to buy goes up 30X in a month
then it comes back down and guess what
it does again right it's like that
launch pattern double bottom bam and
then it takes off again and so you can
go back first let's find this message um
silly oh wait you can see sub three
million this is going to look silly in
the future and people were giving me
clown emojis these are the real clowns
because this went up over 100x from this
entry only almost at 2.91 million market
cap so remember this right here yeah
that is right here right I'm buying Bobo
people are drop uh dropping clown emojis
on my telegram little do they know that
they're the idiots then Bobo 1.1 mil
okay if you go back to Bobo 1.1 mil um
this was right here right you can see it
had this run up pull back still the
double bottom so you can see how my
failure on a previous trade which was
bit bit coin Harry Potter right that
pattern that I [__] up and I didn't
buy it led me to being so crazy about
this pattern and this uh you know
reappearance in Bobo another strong meme
that just made a lot of sense and the
actual Creator and the artist of the
meme was the actual Dev of the meme
which is a huge bonus so um when I run
to this pattern again man I don't
hesitate I don't care how long it took
to pay off I just had a very strong
confidence that it was going to pay pay
off so you can see here Bobo 1.1 million
this can be the god entry right here bot
more today um I've been holding for 3
plus months now and underwater by a
little at the moment but I still think
especially with eth ETF coming eth memes
will have their time and shiny an and
Bobo is one of the best meme options and
so bam 1.1 million bro that is literally
right here right and um and and and mind
you this is whenever I have like way
less people that follow me you know like
way less people know about me anything
um and it goes up from there
um 250X for me averaging in my entries I
got about a 70x so I turned 30k into 2.1
million and then back down today that's
around still worth around a million
dollar okay so I just want you to see
how you know I missed out here but I
didn't cry I didn't weep I didn't say oh
my gosh if only I had gotten it dude dud
the the Market's going to give you
opportunities every single month so I
took this failure and I turned it into
one of the biggest wins ever for me 30k
and a 2.1 million on Bobo so I'd say 90%
of you probably don't even know me uh
back here when I did this trade uh 30k
and a 2.1 million and so this brings me
to my next point which is that obviously
the trade I'm most known for is 15K into
11 million on Brett and I I think most
people know with pretty much almost
certainty that I'm going to turn that
into over $100 million cuz it's pretty
obvious that Brett is going to be one of
the best performing meme coins uh from
this point forward and so this is the
thing right I'm not explaining to the
big trade uh that you mostly know me for
I I took the time to explain to you one
of my mistakes that led me into one of
my biggest wins before Brett actually
and the point of this is for one I don't
want you to repeat the mistake I did on
Harry Potter and just weep and cry about
how you missed an opportunity because
look man I miss peanut recently right
this went from0 to 2 billion and uh
actually though in my leverage telegram
Channel I'm actually long peanut on
Leverage and guess what so go back over
here to my peanut trade same pattern bro
do you notice this look at this so I
missed out on Peanut's first run and
it's very much like the Bobo pattern
it's very much like the Harry Potter
pattern right so you have the runup
right let's just label this uh number
one the runup and then it comes down
bottom one bottom two so let's call this
two three so look at peanut big run up
two and then second bottom right here we
can call it three so basically I saw
peanut major run pulls the [__] back and
then it's starting to out so I entered a
long trade on Peanut and guess what up
over a
180,000 on Peanut so you can see how
these patterns you can take one of your
mistakes and that you can turn that into
the pattern that makes you millions and
millions and by the way you know
actually let's talk about Brett real
quick because I saw the same exact
pattern on Brett early on where once
again has an incredible narrative it
makes complete and total sense and what
we're going to actually need to do is
zoom out to like a 2hour chart scroll
all the way back to the first week of
Brett and you're going to notice the
exact same pattern and so once again
thank goodness I made that mistake on
Harry Potter by the way I almost bought
Harry Potter like I said I mean so close
to being one of the biggest whales in it
I don't care at this point it's fine I
still like that coin even though I don't
own any uh I don't think it's worth
necessarily owning at this exact moment
for me anyways um
and actually we can't see it on this
chart but basically if you if you can
find uh back when Brett's first
started um we can't see it on this chart
but basically Brett I saw had ran to 3
million market cap and then it pulled
back and it was flooring around a 1
million market cap and so same thing
right basically run up double bottom on
a on what on something that made
complete and total sense that had an
incredibly strong narrative that made so
much sense to me right now obviously a
lot of you guys after this video would
probably go find like inverted poopy
butthole coin and you'll see it's pumped
up and then it dumps and then you'll be
like oh man this is the pattern crash
talked about the you know oh you know
buying it and and then it's just going
to end up rugging to zero right and and
then you're going to be like well didn't
work well once again keywords on
something that has a great narrative
that makes complete and total sense
poopy inverted dick hole butthole coin
is not meet the criteria unfortunately
now the criteria of it makes complete in
total sense of course I get it a lot of
people say that's a subjective thing but
whenever you spend hours and hours and
hours and you see thousands and
thousands of coins and meme coins you
know like 99.9% of it is complete [__]
so to me I think it makes a lot of sense
when one out of a million coins you see
it just makes sense it makes complet in
total sense now how do you train that uh
feeling and thought process obviously
it's a great way to start by watching
some of my videos when I actually bought
these coins uh to understand some of the
reasoning and logic that went into them
ultimately wanted to show you a mistake
that led me to making millions of some
of my biggest wins and meme coins now
this pattern literally just popped up
for me on Peanut for example right and I
just shown you I'm up over 180,000 on on
this position here on Leverage and this
is not even buying and holding in the
meme coin this is just a little leverage
trade that I have so these patterns they
pop back up again and they have similar
characteristics and you know when they
repeat you can take them again so
anyways hopefully this has been a little
bit helpful for you but anyways I am now
going uh to to tell you something which
is important which is Bitcoin
maximalists are known for getting into
Bitcoin early
uh you know some people are known for
getting into a Pepe early the Dogecoin
millionaire is known for getting into
Dogecoin uh I am known for getting into
Brett even though so many people they
don't even know me they think this is
like my only trade uh and they don't
even talk about my all my other million
plus dollar mem coin wins so the thing
is what I'm trying to say is if you
immerse yourself into this space you're
on Twitter every day you're staring at
charts all day
you're just consumed your mind is
consumed and you're here constantly
thinking about crypto looking at crypto
and just being around it you are going
to have so many days in the game that
for example you have 300 days in the
game man surely one of those days you're
going to see something and it's going to
resemble for example a pattern that I
have seen or it's going to resemble one
of your own patterns that you've noticed
has work and you're going to say oh my
gosh I know this I have confidence in
this and you're going to get in you're
going to get in with some size and
you're going to make some good money
it's going to happen for you I promise
and this is actually crazy I didn't even
realize this until I I explain this now
that the same exact pattern happened on
Pony when I bought it back to my
telegram let's see Pony 7M cuz this one
I bought in um on Pony so look at this I
said missed the entire first run for
Pony now it's been floored out at 7 mil
for 2 weeks bought some today and will
add over time as long as it stays flored
out like Bobo so you can see once again
has that that bam that initial launch
bam Fizzles out and bottom one bottom
two it just can't go lower anywhere bro
tell me that's not the exact same
pattern that Bitcoin had it's not the
same pattern that bobo had it's not the
same pattern that Brett had early on and
so it's not the same pattern uh that
resistance talk had early on like all my
million plus dollar wins have come from
this pattern and once again Pony
remember I've showed you this now on
Bobo Bitcoin uh and and then bam look
happens again here and so this is
whenever I bought in on Pony around 7
million market cap and then it went up
only from there well not up only it had
a lot of dips actually this run up bam
dips down run up bam dips down double
bottom run up bam dips down double
bottom run up no double bottom here but
yeah man that's crazy so you can see
literally all my million plus dollar
wins have pretty much come from that
pattern major runup on something that is
good something that is legit something
that makes a lot of sense something that
when you think about it you're just like
man like I said it makes complete and
total sense to you you know what I mean
and some things they're not going to
make complete and total sense I'm
talking about the things that make
complete and total sense I know I keep
saying that but a lot of coins you buy
they just don't make sense they're
stupid stupid they have no reason to
have any longevity they have no reason
to be big and so for those things it's
not going to work but on things that
make really good sense that are actually
strong solid narratives that have
quality teams or art or and and and
other things about them and so anyways
I'm really happy I could show you this
and ultimately that was the pattern that
that has helped me a lot and obviously
once again the whole thought process
about the narrative and logic behind
each coin watch some of my other videos
to hear my thought processes as I was
entering a lot of these coins but
ultimately once again it's not going to
your biggest wins are going to come from
being a sheep and just coming on a coin
market cap now there's probably a lot of
newbies who stumbled across this video
and they probably clicked off a while
ago thinking this guy didn't tell me
what website to go and research coins
this guy didn't tell me what wallets to
track this guy didn't tell me this and
this and it's like man let let me go
show you some website bro [__]
everyone else is using that website shut
your damn mouth okay oh tell me the tool
that's going to give me the greatest
100,000x ever crash I mean it's like bro
shut up the greatest tool is your
thought process and what you're seeing
because so many people saw the same
exact plays at me but their thought
process was completely the other
direction they think oh it's dead oh oh
right on Pony oh it's dead oh Harry
Potter oh it looks Dead Oh Bobo oh it
looks dead right everyone you know you
could have [__] used whatever website
you wanted you could have used whatever
special wallet tracking tool you wanted
and you would have still came to the
same conclusion which is this doesn't
look good this looks dead I'm not going
to buy that [__] looks like a [__]
rug and it's like no bro your your
mindset is a rug you're so stupid you're
never going to make money no matter what
tools you're given so the fix here is
not tools it's not a website it's not
wallet tracker it's your mind because
you guys all view this [__] so
incorrectly the biggest money will
always be made when you buy quality [__]
that makes complete and total sense
despite if that thing looks dead despite
if that thing looks like it doesn't have
traction because here's the thing if you
can buy something when it doesn't have
traction and flip it at a much higher
price to people when it does have
traction so that's the thing you don't
actually want to buy things when they
have all the [__] Traction in the
world you want to buy them before they
get much more traction in the future so
truly the T the true test to actually be
able to make millions is when the entire
Market disagrees when the entire Market
is dead when nobody gives a [__] about
the thing you're looking at and you say
you know what all you [__]
looking at these coins in the world
you're all wrong what I have found
despite low volume despite no one giving
a [__] about it I know this is the [__]
when you can stand up against 99% of the
world about a play and say you know what
I have confidence in this I know there's
actual value or there's upside here but
yet the market doesn't realize it today
that is when you will not just win you
will win big okay because anyone can buy
right let's say uh you know the the
market starts getting validated the
market is realizing how undervalued poo
is in relation to Pepe and as it's
running up right people notice oh my
gosh it's validated it is getting you
know the chart tells me it's the truth
now right and so they say oh wow this
really is so undervalued at 500 million
in relation to Pepe at 20 billion right
they'll be like well Bobo's only 140th
the value of Pepe so and then they're
going to say oh I think you get to
1110th
20th you know for example and so later
when they start to get it the thing is
you got it way before them you started
to realize this before them before the
validation before the green candles you
got to you got to get it before others
okay so look um that's all I really got
to say for now um and I hope you enjoyed
the video I apologize that everyone's
looking for ABC checklist um but going
back to this example uh of Bobo right
how at 500 billion and then pep is at 20
billion people can say it's undervalued
it's only at 140th ratio right you see
how all of a sudden people then believe
it people are then willing to pay it for
it at 500 million people are willing to
pay uh for Boba at 1 billion when pep
Pepe is at 20 billion because they still
think it's cheap in relation to Pepe so
you understood something before others
so you can see how this even makes sense
to buy it 1 billion when Pepe is at 20
billion this still makes sense this is
still a good buy you see that's how you
you just got to think far ahead of how
other peoples will view something before
they they ever even know about it right
A lot of people they won't know about
Bobo until it's at 200 million 300
million 400 million or whatever market
cap right but the the key is to front
run and anticipate what will they think
before they even think it and if we can
anticipate that with green candles with
something doing well people are going to
start to look at and say well this is
undervalued in relation to this this is
a really good bet in relation to this
then bam you know they're they're going
to continue buying at a higher price
because it's still going to make sense
then so yeah once again just because
that's not happening this moment doesn't
mean it's not going to happen later you
know how stupid you would be to think
that price action is a reflection of the
truth it's not because if price action
was a reflection of the truth then all
this market cap was was untrue but the
thing is it was true at the time because
not enough not that many people had
realized it then just like right now
there's a lot of people in the world
missing this who still don't realize or
get this now so as long as there's more
people in the future that are going to
find out and understand something it has
upside if now of course if everyone in
the world has already found out and gets
it then the upside has already been
priced in it's it's gone basically you
know um but yeah um that's all I got to
say for now uh to all the people looking
for ABC checklist like I said once again
you're not going to find it in this
video um but um you know this isn't
basketball you don't tuck in your elbow
you don't follow through you know this
is this is not a once again I I think I
said earlier in the video but if there
was an ABC checklist someone would write
a book and we'd all follow ABC and we'd
all be rich that's not how this works
this is not a definitive science um and
that's why I think when there is no
definitive science to back this stuff
the best thing that you can look to is
patterns and then things that make
complete and total sense to you that you
can have confidence in even when the
price is not moving even when things are
just chilling stagnant they're not
[__] doing anything but it still
makes complete and total sense to you so
you your opportunities will come you
will make mistakes you will see a coin
that goes up 1,000x that you saw early
on that you could could have got in and
just keep going and your your time will
come that's pretty much all I have to
say for today um this video is not a
very clean clearcut video
ABC this is how you make a million
dollars of meme coins and uh to be
honest I'm very wary of people like that
U it's not that one two three ABC
like um
and
yeah to be honest if you look at me and
you think I'm just like a dumb kid or
got lucky that should just make you that
much more confident that you're going to
kill it and do way better so this is me
on Twitter if you want to follow me um
and this is really as real as it gets I
don't make these clear edited videos I
just like to share the thoughts raw and
unfiltered and if you like that you can
subscribe and follow me and if not yeah
you're probably not watching this video
so I'll see you guys later take care bye